他可不算是最令人振奮的副總統人選吧
This is not the most inspiring choice for a vice president, right?
瑞秋·麥多秀
他的確是位備受尊敬的官員  務實
I -- I mean, a well-respected operator. Pragmatic.
但老實說
But let's face it.
這也許只是總統對國會的示好
This is probably just a nod to Congress.
提拔一名議員
Tapping one of their own.
下次大選前  他也就是個充數的
It's really nothing more than a placeholder until 2016, assuredly.
我對他私下宣誓就職毫不驚訝
I'm not surprised he's doing a private swearing-in.
我猜總統是想
My bet is that the president wants to draw
儘量保持低調
as little attention to this as possible.
這其中實在沒什麼讓人...
There's just no real wow fa--
克里斯蒂娜怎麼樣
Christina's working out well?
還在適應  不過我目前挺滿意的
She's getting her sea legs, but I've been happy so far.
她很勤奮
She works hard.
她能替我陪總統出行
It's a big load off my shoulders
我可是大大鬆了一口氣
when she can travel with the president instead of me.
我留在這邊更有用武之地
I get so much more done when I stay here.
總統有看好的黨鞭人選嗎
The president have a preference in the whip's race?
沒想到局面會變得這麼不堪
Can't believe how ugly it's gotten.
真讓人無比失望
It was more disappointing than anything.
當心  是啊
Watch out. Yeah, it was.
沒打擾你們吧
I hope I'm not interrupting.
沒有
Not at all.
這可真是不一般
This is something else.
安保要求  他們得趕工  小心
Security specs. They had to work fast. Watch out.
這裡簡直像戰場
It's like a war zone around here.
改建的目的就是隔絕外界影響
The idea is to keep the war from getting in.
黨鞭的競爭怎麼樣了  議員先生
How's the whip's race coming, congressman?
你和霍華德的競爭蠻激烈的
It's tight between you and Howard.
這你得問他
Well you'd have to ask Howard,
不過他大概在忙著琢磨怎麼搞我
if he's not too busy trying to sodomize me.
去打個招呼吧
Shall we go and say hello?
天吶  別逼我跟他說話
For god sakes, don't make me talk to that man.
你好  霍華德
Good to see you, Howard.
見到你真高興  韋斯
Nice to see you, Wes.
高興個屁啊
Yeah. I bet it is.
-鮑勃  -弗蘭克
- Bob. - Frank.
謝謝你邀請我  弗蘭克
Appreciate you inviting me, Frank.
-什麼  -謝謝你邀請我
- What? - Thanks for inviting me.
不客氣
You bet.
法官大人
Judge.
總統及副總統宣誓就職時需由最高法院首席法官見證
你好啊
Good to see you.
有換衣服的地嗎
Is there somewhere I can go to change?
當然有  大廳那邊
Yes, absolutely. There's room down the hall.
道格  照應一下法官
Doug, will you take care of the judge?
他準備好了就趕緊開始
And when he's ready, let's get this thing over with.
我去叫大家進來
I'll start bringing 'em in.
我自願承擔此義務
...that I take this obligation freely,
既無保留  也不逃避
without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion...
我自願承擔此義務
...that I take this obligation freely,
既無保留  也不逃避
without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion...
我將盡職盡責
And that I will well...
離總統只差一步
One heartbeat away from the presidency,
卻不用一張選票
and not a single vote cast in my name.
民主也不過如此
Democracy is so overrated.
完成我的本職工作  上帝保佑
...office on which I am about to enter, so help me God.
我將盡職盡責
And that I will well and faithfully discharge
完成我的本職工作
the duties of the office on which I am about to enter,
上帝保佑
so help me god.
祝賀你  副總統先生
Congratulations, Mr. Vice President.
好了  我們繼續治理國家吧
All right, let's get back to running the country.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
翻譯 草草   somehacker   衛老哥   章魚X
翻譯 喃喃   肉鬆   香茗小焙   小飯
藍光版調整  timhal@HDWinG字幕組   後期 餓得慌
校對 草草   總監 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻譯 HDWinG字幕組修正 請勿去掉製作者資訊
《紙牌屋》
第二季  第二集
你們中一人將接任黨鞭
Now, one of you is gonna replace me as the whip.
你們倆最有希望  大家也知道你們都想爭取
You're the two frontrunners, and we know you both want it.
可你們一點領導風範也沒有
And you're not behaving like men who belong in the leadership.
場面話就別說了
We need to tone down the rhetoric.
你們傷及了黨派利益
You're hurting your party.
我只是在迴應霍華德拋出的謊言
I'm just responding to the lies Howard's been slinging.
公費出遊是真事  韋斯  不是我編的
Those junkets happened, Wes. I'm not making it up.
那你任人唯親呢
And nepotism's any better.
你知道那不是事實
That's just not true, and you know it.
所以你妹夫
And your sister's husband
是湊巧被任命為財務部長了嗎
just happened to be appointed state treasurer.
前妹夫  是的
Ex-husband. And yes.
真是一派胡言  霍華德
That is such a load of crap, Howard.
先生們  鮑勃說的對
Gentlemen, Bob is right.
你倆的鬥爭一旦被曝光
This sort of cat-fighting gets out in the press,
不管誰贏  都不是好事
whichever one of you wins hits the ground limping.
別出陰招了  大家文明一點
Let's keep it clean and bring some civility back to the house.
可以嗎
Can we agree to that?
你倆握個手我會安心一些
I'd feel a lot better if you shook hands on it.
謝謝
Thank you.
我和他在一起呢  克里斯蒂娜
I'm with him right now, Christina.
我走了  我晚些時候去你辦公室
I'm off. I'll swing by your office later.
不用了  還沒裝修好呢
Don't. It's not ready yet.
我就在這兒辦公了
I'll be working from here.
什麼事
What?
塔斯克來了
Tusk is in town.
他45分鐘後和總統會面
He's meeting with the president in 45 minutes.
克里斯蒂娜剛告訴我的
Christina just told me.
商貿聯委會談判的事
The Joint Commission talks.
她就是這麼說的
That's what she said.
克里斯蒂娜還真有用
Christina is proving useful.
我們隨時聯繫
We stay in touch.
給凱茜·杜蘭特打電話
Get me Cathy Durant.
你的人要過來嗎
Your people coming by?
就只有我的新辦公室主任
Just my new chief of staff.
招人之前也沒有別人了
That's all I've got until we hire more.
做副總統的夫人什麼感覺
So how does it feel to be married to the vice president?
完全一樣  就是有點吵
Exactly the same. Just louder.
國務卿杜蘭特
Secretary Durant.
凱西
Cathy.
雷蒙德
Raymond.
祝賀你  副總統先生
Congratulations, Mr. Vice President.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
向你介紹國務卿  杜蘭特
May I please introduce Secretary Durant.
很榮幸  國務卿女士
My pleasure, Madam Secretary.
簡直太意外了
This is quite a surprise.
我根本不知道你來了
I had no idea you were in town.
早上好  總統閣下
Morning, sir.
總統先生
Mr. President.
凱瑟琳
Catherine.
我們剛好撞見了雷蒙德
We just happened to run into Raymond.
太好了
Wonderful.
進來吧
Come on in.
電話記錄肯定能證明我是對的
The phone records will absolutely prove I'm right.
根本就沒有電話記錄  你知道的
There were no phone records. You know that.
那還有運營商的資料歷史記錄
The data history with the carrier.
重新調查根本不可能  就算重新調查了
Even if we got the case reopened, which isn't gonna happen,
你知道要拿到獲取運營商資料的令狀有多難嗎
do you have any idea how hard it is to get a warrant for phone data?
合理理由
Probable cause.
把他找來進行訊問
Bring him in for questioning.
嚴格說這事在你轄區之內
Technically you have jurisdiction.
美國的副總統
The vice president of the United States.
我知道你覺得這很荒謬
I know this all sounds preposterous to you,
但如果你好好看看我的筆記
but if -- if you go through my notes --
我早就看過了
We've been through your notes.
你聽是聽了  但你根本沒聽進去
You've listened. But you haven't heard me.
的確是間接證據  但都合情合理
Circumstantial, yes. But plausible.
我知道你曾為更小的原因重新調查案子
I know you've reopened cases on less.
你必須停手了  哥們
This has gotta stop, man.
我們說來說去就這麼幾句
We keep having the same conversation.
不可能是意外
It can't be an accident.
好吧  我給你看個東西
Okay. I'm gonna show you something.
CNN想拿到這個
CNN tried to get a hold of this.
出於對家屬的尊重  我們拒絕了
We eighty-sixed it out of respect to the family.
監控錄影嗎
The footage?
加密檔案
你看了肯定難受
It's not easy to watch.
我想看
I want to see it.
她要麼是絆倒了  要麼是跳下去的
She tripped. Or jumped.
她不是自殺
She didn't jump.
我逐幀放給你看
Here it is, frame by frame.
還有兩個目擊證人
Now, there were two witnesses.
一個是患眼部黃斑變性的70歲老太太
One was a 70-year-old woman with macular degeneration.
她什麼都沒看清楚
All she saw was a blur.
第二個就是車上的列車員
The second was the conductor of the train.
他說看上去像是她摔倒了
He said it looked like she fell.
除了這兩個證人  就是監控錄影了
I mean between those two and this video, that's all there is.
想看你可以看一萬遍  但是這個案子結了
You can watch it a million times, but this case is closed.
我們得把議程限制在幾個關鍵問題上
We should limit the agenda to a couple of key issues:
工業製品的進口關稅
import tariffs on industrial manufactured goods
以及稀土元素的出口限額
and export quotas on rare earth elements.
他們把這兩個都當做政治槓桿
They're using both as political levers.
我也認為在這兩個問題上我們能有所進展
I agree these are two areas where we can make meaningful progress.
但我更擔心針對企業的網路攻擊的增加
But I'm worried about the rise in corporate cyber attacks.
扯上這個就沒完了
That's a rabbit hole.
我們早晚得說這件事
Well, we have to address it sooner or later.
問題是我們要不要現在談這個
It's just a matter of whether we want to address it now.
中國人不喜歡意外
The Chinese don't like surprises.
我只是想說
All I'm proposing is that
我們現在利用商貿聯委會談判委婉地提出這個問題
we use the Joint Commission talks to bring it up gently now,
為下輪談判做好鋪墊
set the stage for the next round.
我是個商人  不是外交官
Look, I'm a businessman, not a diplomat.
但是我是個在中國工作了35年的商人
But I'm a businessman with 35 years experience working in China.
和他們談判  不能太貪心
When they come to the table, you don't get greedy.
你在福建有一個合資煉油廠
You're working on a co-venture refinery project in Fujian.
這也是業內首家
Which would be the first of its kind.
放開了增加投資的渠道...
Open the gateway for increased investment --
網路攻擊對那些合作企業構成威脅
Cyber attacks threaten those co-ventures.
如果中方可以通過
There's less a need for them
商業間諜活動獲取新技術  也就無需合作了
if the Chinese can obtain new technology from corporate espionage.
弗蘭克  你覺得呢
Frank, what do you think?
我更傾向於雷蒙德的想法
I lean more toward Raymond's thinking.
如果引起中方的反感  那多年的努力都白費了
If we antagonize the Chinese we could undo years of progress.
我可以低調行事  絕不會使強硬手腕
Allow me to do this quietly, with a soft touch.
我不會激怒他們  先生
I won't antagonize them, sir.
我們最不需要的就是自找麻煩
The last thing we want to do is rock the boat.
你想怎麼辦  凱瑟琳
What do you have in mind, Catherine?
建議性議程
A suggested agenda.
而不是作為要求
Not a demand.
這件事由中層出面  我根本不插手
We'll keep it mid-level. I won't get anywhere near it.
雷蒙德
Raymond?
我已經表明瞭顧慮
I've voiced my concerns.
-要格外謹慎剋制  -我向你保證  先生
- A very soft touch. - You have my word, sir.
好
Good.
雷蒙德  一起吃個午餐吧
Raymond? Want to grab some lunch?
樂意之極
Would love to.
謝謝  弗蘭克  歡迎加入白宮
Thanks, Frank. Welcome to the West Wing.
謝謝你  先生
Thank you, sir.
總統就像曠野上的一棵孤樹
The president is like a lone tree in an empty field.
風往哪吹  他就往哪倒
He leans whichever way the wind is blowing.
現在雷蒙德·塔斯克的西風吹得實在太猛
And right now Raymond Tusk blows far too strong from the west.
那是假髮嗎
Is that a wig?
不是  他都留了好幾個月了
No. He's been growing it out for months.
戴安說她喜歡長髮
Diane says she likes it long.
我告訴她  等她看到
I told her she'll feel differently
他留起長髮辯就會改主意了
once she sees the first dread lock.
或者聞到
Or smells it.
我上週去看了你女兒
I went to see your daughter last weekend.
她怎麼樣
How is she?
-想看看照片嗎  -好啊
- You want to see a picture? - Okay.
-她媽媽在嗎  -對
- Was her mother there? - Yeah.
他們的錢夠用吧
Are they okay on money?
格林伍茲的保險率費一月份要上調了
The rate at Greenwoods is going up in January.
凱特琳娜擔心錢不夠用
Catalina is worried she's gonna be short.
我會多打點去她賬上
I'll make sure to put more into the account.
如果你不舒服  我們不用聊她
We don't have to talk about her if you don't...
不不  沒事  我很感謝你去看她
No, no, no. It's fine. I appreciate you going to see her.
抱歉  泰德
I'm sorry, Ted.
你邀我一起吃午餐  我以為你是想...
I thought that when you asked me to lunch it was because you want --
不不  沒錯
No, no, no. I mean, yes,
我想確保她們的需求都得到滿足
I want to make sure they have what they need.
但是  不
But, no,
我想找你談是為了...
the reason I wanted to talk --
洛莉·塔特
Lorrie Tate.
洛莉是我朋友  她怎麼了
Lorrie's a friend of mine. What about her?
她說你有意競選黨鞭
She mentioned you're interested in the whip's race.
天吶
Oh, no.
真希望她沒這麼說
I wish she hadn't.
為什麼
Why not?
因為很荒唐啊
Because it's ridiculous.
是嗎
Is it?
我只是隨口說說
I just mentioned it off-hand.
韋斯和巴克沃特的競爭簡直...
The whole Webb and Buchwalter thing is just --
一團糟
Complete mess.
但我是開玩笑的
But I wasn't serious.
我覺得你該認真想想
I think you should be serious.
你想競選黨鞭嗎
Do you want to do it?
我沒有經驗啊  泰德  我還...
I don’t have the experience, Ted. And I -- I --
想不想
Yes or no?
當然想
Yes, of course.
將來再說
Someday.
但現在  我沒有他們那樣的財力
But now I -- I don't have the money they do.
你用我的錢  就有了
Unless you use mine.
你不能把你的錢浪費在...
You can't waste your money on --
如果我找到那些還持觀望態度的人
If I funnel my PAC money to
把我的政治行動委員會資金給他們一些
some folks who are on the fence,
在你正式宣佈前  拉攏一些支持者
round up a couple dozen commitments before you announce,
那你立刻就是有力競爭者
that would make you an instant contender.
你說這是浪費嗎
Now tell me that's a waste.
這可是千百萬啊
We're talking hundreds of thousands.
這可不是聖誕禮物  傑姬
It's not a Christmas present, Jackie.
如果你是黨鞭  我就在領導層有了堅定的盟友
With you as whip I have a strong ally in the leadership.
我的獲益不比你少
I stand to gain as much as you.
稍等片刻
Hang on one second.
我不知道哪裡...
I don't know where the...
怎麼樣  他信了嗎
How did it go? Did he buy it?
不管你給他吹了什麼風  吹得很到位
Whatever bug you put in his ear burrowed deep.
很簡單  那人喜歡你  對你視如己出
It was easy. The man adores you like you're his own child.
但你可得選我做首席副黨鞭
But you sure as hell better make me Chief Deputy.
我得先當選
I need to win first.
我和泰德兩票  還剩111票
Ted and I make two. 111 to go.
副黨鞭會數數總是好事
It's always good when the Chief Deputy knows her arithmetic.
別扯淡  我們數票吧
Fuck off. Let's start taking names.
這個還不錯
This one seems promising.
康納·埃利斯  可靠  有經驗
Connor Ellis. He's solid. Good experience.
是他解決了瓊斯參議員
Oh, he's the one that got Senator Jones out of that mess
借調查名義影響民意的民意調查
推手民調的爛攤子
with the push polling.
是啊  免受紀律委員會的調查
Yes. Kept him from the ethics committee.
面試一下吧
Let's set up an interview.
我安排一下日程
I'll find a good time in schedule.
我們說說日程的事
Let's talk about the schedule.
好好挑一下我該參加哪些活動
I think we need to be more selective with the events I do.
有些是上任副總統夫人沒去成的
Some of these are leftovers from Mrs. Matthews.
你想取消也可以
We can cancel whatever you like.
這是什麼
And what's this?
你丈夫要為兩位新晉海軍陸戰隊將軍授銜
Your husband will be pinning stars on two newly commissioned Marine generals.
這個你應該去
I think that's one you should do.
給我介紹一下
Okay. Walk me through it.
兩位將軍分別是艾莉西婭·漢普頓
The generals are Alicia Hampton
和道頓·麥金尼斯
and Dalton McGinnis.
6點50到場
Arriving at 6:50 --
道頓·麥金尼斯嗎
Dalton McGinnis?
是的  認識嗎
Yes. Do you know him?
大學同學
We went to college together.
剛說到哪了
I'm sorry, where were we?
什麼時候到
Arrive what time?
6點50
6:50.
很好  出席人員名單給我一份
Great. I'd like a list of all the people that will be attending.
我被排除在外沒什麼
It's not that big a deal if I get left out,
可你是國務卿啊
but you're the secretary of state.
塔斯克怎麼能參與決策
I mean, Tusk should not be determining policy.
只有總統可以決定你該怎麼做
The president alone should instruct you on what you are to pursue.
他們什麼關係
What's their relationship?
他一直給總統出謀劃策
He's had his ear for years.
提建議
An advisor...
更像是導師  總統很重視他的建議
More of a mentor. And one whose advice is not easily dismissed.
他還會繼續要求忽視網路戰
He's gonna keep pushing back on cyber warfare.
除非我給提上議程
Not if I get it on the agenda.
不  你提上議程他更會來勁
No, especially if you get it on the agenda.
商貿聯委會談判再度開啟時
Tusk is not gonna take any chances
塔斯克絕不會冒絲毫風險
when the next Joint Commission talks come around.
你剛剛不是支援他嗎
You agreed with him in the meeting.
如果我們站一邊  他的態度只會更強硬
If we had ganged up, he would have taken a firmer position.
說不定
For all we know,
他現在就在勸總統改主意呢
he's convincing the president right now to change his mind.
所以我們絕不能給他機會
Now we need to remove that option as a possibility.
怎麼辦
How?
下次談判時  強迫中方迴應網路安全問題
Force the Chinese to confront the issue now, this round of talks.
我答應總統不採取強硬手段的
I promised the president a soft touch.
我不能有意食言
I can't intentionally break my promise.
如果是無意的呢
What if it was unintentional?
凱茜  如果你不喜歡現在的局勢
Cathy, if you don't like how the table is set,
就乾脆攪局
turn over the table.
你偷吸
You're cheating.
哪有  是電子煙
No, I'm not. It's vapor.
那也算
Still.
你該試試
You should try it.
會上癮  但沒副作用
Addiction without the consequences.
你自己抽
It's all yours.
不睡嗎
You staying up?
明晚的授銜儀式
This ceremony tomorrow night.
你不想去
You don't want to go.
除非我必須去
If I don't have to.
我也不喜歡
I hate these sorta things, too.
但這是副總統的首次亮相
But it is my first public appearance as vice president.
好吧
Okay.
謝謝
Thank you.
要不要把這兒改成辦公室
Should we turn this into a proper office?
可以啊  樓下沒有私密性
That's not a bad idea. No privacy downstairs.
我去找裝修隊
I'll talk to the contractor.
晚安  弗蘭西斯
Goodnight, Francis.
晚安
Goodnight.
先生  先生  根據國會議事錄
Sir! Sir! Congressional Record.
不是要談到六點嗎
Weren't the talks supposed to go until six?
他們不聽  我們談不下去
We can't talk if they won't listen.
中方不談了嗎
Did the Chinese walk out?
我們已經表明  除非他們肯談政府資助的
We made it clear that we won't discuss any other issues
網路攻擊  否則其他問題免談
until government-sponsored cyber attacks are on the table.
顯然他們不開心了
Apparently that's not what they wanted to hear.
中方代表離席之前你說了什麼
Sir, what did you tell the Chinese delegation before they walked out?
我們沒派人去
We didn't have anybody there.
商貿聯委會談判通常很無聊的
The Joint Commission is usually a snooze-fest.
今天不是
Not today it wasn't.
我已經讓格里爾去弄了
I've got Greer on it.
這不是國際板塊的新聞嗎
Isn't this international?
如果要寫網路戰的背景資料
We need somebody from the tech beat
就得請科技板塊的記者
if we want any background on cyber warfare.
他找到人接受署名採訪了嗎
Does he have anybody on record yet?
中方不肯談
The Chinese aren't talking.
美國代表團的話美聯社都報道了
And all the U.S. delegation said is what's in the AP wire.
無論如何兩小時內網上要出報道
I want something online in the next two hours.
本週內發一篇深入後續報道
In-depth follow-up sometime this week.
盧卡斯  你還好嗎
Hey, Lucas? You all right?
好啊  怎麼了
Yeah. Why?
你還穿著昨天穿的那身
You're wearing the same clothes you wore yesterday.
是嗎
Am I?
我不知道你私生活發生了什麼
I don't know what's going on in your personal life,
但似乎已經影響到你的工作了
but it seems to be entering the workplace.
儀表很重要
Appearances matter.
我們的編輯不能比他的記者
And we can't have an editor looking more disheveled
還不修邊幅
than his reporters.
兩小時  一定給你個交待
Two hours. You'll have something.
你知道傑姬·夏普要競選黨鞭嗎
Did you know Jackie Sharp's running for Whip?
不知道  這是我第一次聽說
No, this is the first I'm hearing of it.
我跟韋伯說了
I spoke to Webb.
洛莉·塔特給他發了一封關於我的電郵
He got an email from Lorrie Tate about me.
戴夫·霍蘭德給我發了一封關於他的電郵
I got one from Dave Holland about him.
這我不管
Which means nothing to me.
公費旅遊  任人唯親  塔特跟夏普很親密
The junkets, the nepotism. Tate and Sharp are close.
霍蘭德跟她在退伍軍人事務委員會共事過
Holland serves on the VA committee with her.
她找別人出手  好撇清干係
She used proxies to insulate herself.
你覺得是她把料爆給了他們
So you think that she gave the dirt to them.
沒錯  她在耍我們兩個人
Yeah. She's been playing both of us.
你覺得她能拉到多少支持者
How many commitments do you think she could have?
目前也就20個左右吧
Around 20 so far.
那她還是被你倆遠遠甩在後面啊
So she's a distant third.
但她在一個個動搖我們的支持者啊
But she's picking people off us left and right.
你得幫我
I want your help.
我支援你啊  韋斯
You have my support, Wes.
那就公開表態
Then make that public.
如果我公開支援你  博奇就會支援韋伯
If I come out for you, Birch comes out for Webb.
那反倒會害你  而不是幫你
That's gonna hurt you, not help you.
情況很不妙  弗蘭克
This is serious, Frank.
泰德·哈維梅耶在贊助她
Ted Havemeyer is bankrolling her.
你想過跟傑姬談談嗎
Have you thought of talking to Jackie?
沒有  原則上我不能那麼做
No, no. I can't do that on principle.
為什麼不行
Why not?
我不會跟哈維梅耶支援的人合作
Anyone who Havemeyer is backing, I don't work with.
我競選參議員的時候  他也攪了我的局
He pulled the same crap on me when I ran for Senate.
他贊助我的主要對手  混蛋
He financed my primary opponent. Asshole.
那由你決定
Well, that is your call.
但如果你要讓舊賬阻礙你的競選
But if you're gonna let an old grudge get in the way of progress --
我就是不能這麼做  弗蘭克
I just can't do it, Frank.
哈維梅耶這些年一直想把我趕下去
Havemeyer's been trying to shove me down the totem pole for years.
我不會讓他得逞的
I won't give him the satisfaction.
我尊重你  但這樣我就無能為力了
Well, I can respect that, but my hands are tied.
這件事很微妙
It's a delicate matter,
但我們正在和中國政府溝通
but we are in communication with the Chinese government
如何推進談判
as to how to move forward.
這是不是表示美國將在網路攻擊的事上屈服
Does this mean the U.S. will back down on cyber attacks?
美國從不屈服
The United States never backs down,
特別是在重要問題上
particularly on issues that are high priority to us.
國務卿女士  您是怎麼
Madam Secretary, what did you--
謝謝
Thank you.
您是怎麼跟代表團團長說的
What did you tell the head of the delegation?
代表團越界了
The delegation overstepped its bounds,
但凱茜不能坑她自己的人
but Cathy couldn’t throw her own people under the bus.
她公開發表言論前該先跟我們商量一下
She should have consulted us first before speaking publicly.
媒體堵在她家門口
The press was on her doorstep
總統又在地球另一端
and the president was in another hemisphere.
我不是在批評她的做法
Now, look, I'm not condemning what she did,
但她總得採取措施
but she had to do something.
她憑直覺做決定  並採取了行動
She made a gut call and she acted.
咱們得撇清關係
We have to distance ourselves from this.
總統什麼時候回來
When is the president back?
明天早上
Tomorrow morning.
我們能安排一次會面嗎
Can we set up a meeting?
凱茜得公開道歉
Cathy needs to publicly apologize.
我們能讓她跟總統談談嗎
Can we get her in the room with the president?
我們不應該先統一一下步調嗎
Shouldn't we all be on the same page first?
我再想想辦法吧
I'll see what I can do.
謝謝
Thank you.
我去拿吃的之前  你問我了一個問題
Now, you asked me a question before I went and got my food.
副總統先生  我是麥金尼斯將軍
Mr. Vice President. General McGinnis.
不勝榮幸  希望你不介意
it's a great honor. I hope you don't mind.
總統也想出席  他讓我代為參加
The president wishes he could be here. He's asked me to fill in.
榮幸的是我  先生
The honor is mine, sir.
將軍  這是我妻子  克萊爾
And, General, this is my wife, Claire.
很高興見到你  克萊爾  好久不見
It's good to see you, Claire. It's been a long time.
是啊
Yes.
哈佛的同學
Harvard. We were classmates.
克萊爾沒提過這事
Claire didn't say a thing.
我們還約會過
We dated for a time.
只有五分鐘
About five minutes.
好了  不打擾你們用餐了
Anyway, I'll let you get back to your meal.
謝謝  我想起來了
Thank you. I've remembered.
有意思的是
Interestingly enough,
南卡羅萊納州第一大作物不是棉花
in South Carolina the largest crop is not cotton.
而是菸草
No. It's tobacco.
第三大作物是大麻
And the third-largest crop is marijuana.
咱心裡明白就好
Now -- we'll just keep that to ourselves.
失陪一下
Would you all excuse me for just a moment?
-只有她一個嗎  -是的
- Is she alone? - Yes.
我們想單獨談談
Would you give us a few moments, please?
怎麼了
What's wrong?
是他
It was him.
誰
Who?
大一那年
Freshman year.
那件事...是麥金尼斯嗎
You mean... McGinnis?
弗蘭西斯  弗蘭西斯  別做傻事
Francis, Francis. Please, don't do anything.
我絕不會給他授銜...
I am not gonna pin a medal on that --
你必須授銜
You have to.
等一下  不能讓他
Just a minute, please! There is no way that man --
先生  典禮要開始了
Sir, they want to start the ceremony.
等一會兒  他不配接受...
Just a minute, please! He does not deserve a medal..
弗蘭西斯  求你了
Francis. I beg of you.
我告訴你  槍斃他都不過分
I'm telling you, that man deserves to be taken out and shot.
我求你了
I am begging you.
-不行  -求你了
- No. - Please!
-不要  -別...
- No. - Do not --
我說等等
I said just a minute!
求你了  別惹事
Do not make a scene. Please.
湯姆  謝謝你能來
Tom. Thanks for coming by.
我走進來時  我以為會有一絲懷念
You know, I thought I would miss this place the moment I stepped inside.
可是沒有
But I don't.
喝斯黛拉沒問題吧
Hope you like Stella.
乾杯
Cheers.
Beers up.
你怎麼樣
How are things?
還不錯  還不錯
They're good. They're good.
你開心嗎
You're happy?
我就沒開心過
I haven't been happy a day in my life.
不過現在有時間了
But I have time now.
可以思考  寫作  我最近在構思小說
To think. To write. Been working on a novel.
是嗎
Yeah?
純粹是狗屁  不過還湊合
It's absolute shit. That's okay.
挺好的  湯姆  真挺好的
That's great, Tom. That's really great.
有什麼事
What's on your mind?
找我來不是敘舊的吧
I know you didn't ask me here just to catch up.
弗蘭克·安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
我萬分榮幸地
On the president's behalf
代表總統  授予艾莉西婭·漢普頓將軍
it is my great honor to formerly recognize the selection
美軍歐洲司令部
of General Alicia Hampton as Commander,
司令一職
United States European Command,
授予道頓·麥金尼斯將軍
and General Dalton McGinnis
美國戰略司令部司令一職
as Commander of the United States Strategic Command.
兩位模範領袖為美國海軍陸戰隊
The United States Marine Corps has been well served
做出了卓越貢獻
by these two exemplary leaders.
總統與我希望兩位再接再厲
The president and I are grateful for their continued service.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
謝謝你  先生
Thank you, sir.
你覺得我瘋了嗎
You think I'm insane?
我不覺得你瘋了
I don't think you're insane.
只是經歷了太多痛苦
I think you've been through a lot.
想探個究竟
Trying to make sense of it all.
我知道我是對的
I know I'm right.
那是自然
I'm sure I believe you are.
酒駕的事的確是他掩蓋的
It's a fact that he helped cover up the DUI.
如果你手下的記者拿著這事來找你
Imagine if one of your reporters came to you with this story.
你會登出去嗎
Could you print a word of it?
不會  但會要求他們繼續調查
No, but I'd have them keep digging.
是嗎
Would you?
憑心而論
If you're honest with yourself,
你不會說這故事太牽強了嗎
wouldn't you tell them it seemed farfetched?
筆記說明不了什麼
Your notes aren't convincing.
警方報告也證實不了什麼
The police reports don't prove a link.
-還有你的妄加猜測  -我知道
- And the speculative leaps you're making... - I know.
律人要先律己
Hold yourself to the same standards as you hold your staff.
你當時在和佐伊約會
You and Zoe were seeing each other.
我是猜的  也許錯了
I -- I'm assuming. Maybe I'm wrong.
是在約會
We -- we were.
第一任妻子去世時  我也接受不了
When I lost my first wife, it didn't add up.
誰會在31歲就死於乳腺癌呢
Who dies of breast cancer at 31?
我想起訴  告醫生  醫院  所有人
I wanted to sue. Doctors, the hospital, everyone.
覺得他們在隱瞞什麼
Thought they were hiding something.
但沒有
No.
悲傷讓人想要答案  但有時真的就沒有
Grief demands an answer, but sometimes there isn't one.
沒人能挽救她  就是這樣
Her life couldn't be saved. Period.
我該怎麼辦
What do I do?
你願找人談談嗎
Would you consider seeing someone?
辛西婭去世時
There's a therapist who helped me a great deal
有個醫生幫了我很多
when Cynthia passed away.
我可以幫你聯繫...
I can put you in touch --
不了  我不用見誰
No. I don't need to see somebody.
盧卡斯
Lucas.
很感謝你過來  湯姆
I appreciate you coming by, Tom.
也謝謝你的啤酒
Thanks for the beer.
隨時聯繫我吧
You call me anytime.
照顧好自己  盧卡斯
You take care of yourself, Lucas.
我是認真的
I mean it.
還打算去哪嗎  先生
Any plans to go elsewhere, sir?
不了  我們今晚不出去了  謝謝
No. We're in for the night. Thank you.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
我累了
I'm tired.
需要什麼嗎  先生
Do you need something, sir?
我的遙控手柄  我想玩遊戲
Uh, my remote. I want to play.
就在這兒
It's right over here.
謝謝
Thank you.
網路出問題了嗎  我上不了線
Is there something wrong with the Internet? I can't get online.
我們封掉了連線
We had to disable the access.
那個連線不安全
It's not a secure connection.
能讓我單獨待會兒嗎
Could you just give me a moment, please?
只要您在外面  身邊就得有人
Whenever you're out here, somebody needs to be with you.
我在自家後院都不能獨自待著嗎
I can't be alone in my own backyard?
我說了算倒可以  但我說了不算
If it were up to me, sir. But it's not up to me.
好吧  密查姆
Okay, Meechum.
你以為我不想摔東西嗎
You think I don't want to smash things?
我的憤怒是你無法想象的
I know what that anger is more than you can imagine.
他壓著我的時候...
When he was on top of me --
我們不需要說這個
We don't have to talk about it.
不  我想說
No, I want to.
他壓著我的時候  我使勁推
When he was on top of me, I pressed my hand --
用盡全力推他的臉
with everything I could I pressed it into his face.
我使足了勁  弄傷了他的鼻子
I pressed it so hard I broke his nose.
但那沒能阻止他
That didn't stop him.
他把床單塞進我嘴裡
He shoved the sheets in my mouth.
我幾乎無法呼吸
I could barely breathe.
每次我想起那個女孩
Every time I think of her
被人那樣按倒
pinned down like that
我都會勒死她  弗朗西斯
I strangle her, Francis,
這樣她才不會勒死我
so she doesn't strangle me.
我必須那樣  我們必須那樣
I have to. We have to.
否則...
The alternative is --
我無法忍受
it's unlivable.
你該休息了
You should go to sleep.
我不知道能不能睡著
I'm not sure if I can.
那你就回樓下去
Then you should go back downstairs.
早晨的時候  恨意也不會消退
You'll still feel the hate in the morning.
你會利用那份恨意  但不是去報復他
You'll use that. But not on him.
你到底說了什麼
What did you communicate, exactly?
我讓他提出議事日程
I told him to bring up the agenda,
指出戰略對話的關鍵點  但別提要求
suggest bullet points for the SED, but make no demands.
那怎麼會被理解成最後通牒
And how did that translate into a direct ultimatum?
有時我的代表會探究言外之意
Well, sometimes my delegates try to read between the lines.
他們知道我為外交目的需要合理推卸責任
They know that I need plausible deniability for diplomatic purposes.
那你為什麼沒有立刻否認
Why didn't you immediately recant?
就我跟中國人打交道的經驗看
In my experience with the Chinese,
變卦會讓他們覺得我們軟弱
backpedaling makes us look weak.
我當時有兩個選擇  丟臉或展示實力
I had two choices: Lose face or exhibit strength.
我選擇了後者
I chose the latter.
好吧  凱瑟琳  我會很快跟你聯繫
All right, Catherine. I'll be in touch shortly.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
用我的私人線路打給雷蒙德
Get me Raymond on the private line.
你覺得她是故意越界的嗎
Do you think she overstepped on purpose?
凱茜絕不會違反你的指令  不會故意違反
Cathy would never disobey your orders. Not on purpose.
雷蒙德  弗蘭克在我這兒
Raymond, I've got Frank here.
就我們三個嗎
Just the three of us?
就三個  早上好  雷蒙德
Just us three. Morning, Raymond.
我在北京的聯繫人
My contacts in Beijing
跟我說商務部部長很激動
tell me the minister of commerce is in a tizzy.
他想以此為藉口重拳出擊
Wants to use this as an excuse to start clenching fists.
我要麼拆凱茜的臺  要麼支援她
Well, either I turn my back on Cathy or I stand behind her.
選前者
It's gotta be the former.
我同意
I agree.
如果你不道歉
If you don't apologize,
那就不是小矛盾  而是大摩擦了
you go from ruffling feathers to plucking them.
中國人絕不會忍氣吞聲  總統先生
And the Chinese won't stand for that, Mr. President.
說是我跟內閣之間意思傳達有錯誤如何
What about perceived miscommunication between me and my cabinet?
總統先生  現在的目標是繼續談判
Mr. President, right now the goal is to resume the talks.
就別擔心他們是怎麼想的了
I wouldn't worry about perceptions.
弗蘭克沒錯  我們得現實點
Frank is right. We need to be pragmatic.
先別擔心場面上的事
Worry about appearances later.
行  我讓凱瑟琳擬一份致歉信
All right. I'll have Catherine draft an apology.
不  必須由你親自寫  總統先生
No, it has to come from you, Mr. President.
道歉要有份量
If the apology is to mean anything,
就得由白宮出面
it must come from the White House.
這樣的確應該更有成效
That is certainly the more likely to succeed.
行  那我親自寫  謝謝  雷蒙德
Fine. I'll do it then. Thank you, Raymond.
謝謝你  加勒特
Thank you, Garrett.
你聽到他仍然直呼總統的名字嗎
Do you hear how he still uses the president's given name?
而沃克也毫不在意他的失敬
And that Walker doesn't flinch at the lack of respect it implies.
先生  恕我直言
Sir, forgive me if this isn't the case,
你好像有點猶豫
but you seem a bit hesitant.
為什麼這麼說
Why do you say that?
關於公眾看法的事  你所言極是
Well, you've raised a good point about public perception.
我不想讓你覺得
I don't want you to think that
我對你的擔憂毫不在意
I'm dismissing your concerns casually.
沒有  你也擔心這個嗎
No. It's a concern for you, too?
凱茜提出的觀點不無道理
There is some insight into what Cathy brought up.
變卦就是軟弱
Backpedalling is weakness.
跟中國人合作總是碰運氣
Well, it's always a coin toss with the Chinese.
但有時候堅定立場比讓步妥協要好
But sometimes standing your ground is better than giving in.
你強勢  他們反而更尊重你
They respect you more when you show strength.
你改變對此的看法了嗎  弗蘭克
Are you changing your mind on this, Frank?
我只是覺得  你該按自己的心意決定
I just think it's important that you do what you think is best.
美國人民選你當總統
The American people voted you president.
不是我  也不是雷蒙德·塔斯克
Not me. Not Raymond Tusk.
我決定了再告訴你
I'll let you know what I decide.
謝謝  總統先生
Thank you, sir.
你覺得安德伍德會選她嗎
You think she's Underwood's choice?
他沒直說  所以有可能
He deflected, so it's possible.
你和我
You and I,
我們得合作  韋斯
we need to work together on this, Wes.
否則我們倆都得完蛋
Before we both get screwed.
我同意
I agree.
我們中一個人退出
One of us drops out,
支援另一個人
throws support to the other.
這就能削弱她的支援力量
That'll dwarf any following she has.
你想讓我退出嗎
You want me to drop out.
我一定任命你做眾議院撥款委員會主席
I'll make sure you get my chairmanship on appropriations.
你至多能任命我做紀律委員會主席  這沒人稀罕
All you can offer me is, uh, Ethics, which nobody wants.
我們把事定下來吧  韋斯
Let's put this to bed, Wes.
韋伯肯定跟他談了協議
Webb must have offered him a deal.
那我們就提出更好的條件
Then we have to offer a better one.
我猜是撥款委員會  我給不了更好的
I'm guessing appropriations. There's no way I can top that.
除非是眾議院稅賦委員會
Except for ways and means.
我不能讓你把職位給巴克沃特這樣的混蛋
I -- I won't let you give your chair to an ass like Buchwalter.
如果你是黨鞭
If you're the Whip,
你地位比他  和其他主席都高
you outrank him and every other chairman.
去他的委員會
Screw committees.
我能直接跟議長交流
I'll have a direct line to the speaker.
別固執了  傑姬
Don't be stubborn, Jackie.
你覺得他會接受嗎
You think he'd take it?
他連韋伯的條件都願意接受
He was willing to take a deal from Webb.
但你是他最討厭的人
But you're the only person he hates more.
他很蠻人  但不是傻子
He's a brute. But he's not an idiot.
我知道你不是出於忠誠而拒絕
Well, I know you're not refusing out of loyalty.
沒錯
True.
所以是泰德的緣故
So it's because of Ted.
你覺得自己很厲害  對吧
You think you are hot shit, don't you?
我們能放下架子  像成年人那樣談正經事嗎
Can we set egos aside and talk business like the adults we are?
我想要的不只是稅賦委員會主席之位
I want more than ways and means.
說吧
Tell me.
我要哈維梅耶走人  不只是退休
I want Havemeyer gone. Not just retired....
讓他從政壇消失
Politically dead.
競選是12年前的事了
That race was 12 years ago.
不是他  我也能當12年參議員了
That was 12 years I could have been in the Senate.
你就想報復  真的嗎
Revenge? Really?
不是報復
Not revenge.
是報應
Equity.
那你準備怎麼辦
Well, what are you gonna do?
巴克沃特不會讓步的
Buchwalter won't budge.
我這一生最鄙視小氣之人
You know, there's nothing I despise more in life than pettiness.
我可以去找韋伯  但我給不了他什麼
I could approach Webb, but I don't have enough to offer him.
他不會退選的  他自尊心太強
Ah, he'd never drop out. Too much pride.
我不知道該怎麼辦
I'm not sure what to do.
這是泰德的檔案  他有個私生女
This is my file on Ted. An illegitimate daughter.
和保姆生的
The nanny, of course.
她叫艾米莉·羅德里格斯  19歲了
Her name is Emily Rodriguez. 19.
患腦中風
Cerebral palsy.
我知道艾米莉的事
I know about Emily.
那我們還在這裡討論什麼
Well, then why are we having this conversation?
這說來話長
It's complicated.
私生女  我沒看出有什麼複雜的
The daughter? It's very black and white to me.
我跟泰德是一輩子的交情
I've known Ted since I was born.
他跟我父親是好友
He and my father were very close.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I'm aware.
他一直都對我關照有加
He's always looked out for me.
他把我送進西點軍校  資助我第一次競選
He got me into West Point. He funded my first race.
我喜歡泰德  他一直都很有團隊精神
I like Ted. He's always been a team player.
很不幸  他擁有這樣的祕密
It's unfortunate he has this secret.
這是個錯誤  他一直都很後悔
It was a mistake. One he's always regretted.
她出生之後  他讓我去探望她
After she was born he asked me to check in on her,
因為他自己做不到  而他信任我
because he couldn't. Because he trusted me.
我懂了
I see.
你來這裡的時候就知道你該做什麼
You came in here knowing what you had to do,
但你還是希望我能變個戲法  你就不用那麼做了
hoping I would pull a rabbit out of a hat so you wouldn't have to.
我認識這姑娘  我認識她母親
I know the girl. I know her mother.
她們不該經受那種事
These people don't deserve this.
我該支的招都支了
I've given you all I can.
你要如何決定是你自己的事
Whatever you decide is your prerogative.
但也許我錯看了你
But maybe I misjudged you.
泰德對我來說就像家人一樣
Ted is family to me.
用來取代親生女兒的養女
An adopted daughter in lieu of a real one.
先生  國務卿來了
Sir, the secretary is here.
謝謝  讓她進來  你下去吧
Thank you. Send her in. Excuse us.
很好
It's good.
是不是太長了
Not too long?
有一點  但也還好
A little bit, but not much.
這部分  三個段落
This part, three paragraphs in.
關於電話公司嗎
Oh, about the phone companies?
多跟我講講
Tell me more.
這是國土安全部的主要擔憂之一
It's one of Homeland Security's major concerns.
網路攻擊會滲透到電話運營商
That the cyber attacks might infiltrate phone carriers,
得到數百萬人的資料記錄
get access to millions of people's data history.
比如他們跟誰通過電話嗎
Like who they called?
是的  跟誰通過電話  發過簡訊
Yeah, who they called, texted,
簡訊是什麼內容
what they texted,
何時  何地  所有資訊
when, where they were. Everything.
有這種可能嗎
And that's possible?
目前沒有嚴重的資訊洩露事件
There haven't been any catastrophic breaches yet.
至少沒有相關報道
At least not reported.
但是中國似乎已經開始
But it looks like the Chinese are starting to
在深網上招募僱傭黑客
recruit mercenaries on the Deep Web
發動無法追蹤的網路游擊戰
to launch guerilla-type attacks that can't be tracked back --
等一下  深網  我聽說過
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. The Deep Web. I've heard of that.
是的
Oh, yeah, yeah.
96%的網路內容無法通過
No, 96% of the internet isn't accessible
普通引擎搜索到  這其中大部分毫無價值
through standard search engines. Most of it's useless.
但是在那裡你幾乎可以找到任何東西
But it's where you go to find anything and everything.
兒童色情片  位元幣洗錢  郵購麻醉劑
Child porn, Bitcoin laundering, mail-order narcotics,
僱傭黑客
hackers for hire.
怎麼進入深網
How do you access it?
其實很簡單  你想看的話我可以演示
It's actually pretty easy. I could show you if you want.
好啊  我很好奇
Yeah, I'm curious.
我能不能...
Mind if I...?
請便
Go ahead.
好  首先你需要洋蔥路由
Okay, first thing you need is TOR.
有些人喜歡隱形網  但我覺得洋蔥路由更好
Some people prefer I2P, but I think TOR is better.
洋蔥路由是什麼
What is TOR?
它可以通過代理伺服器保護你  讓你匿名
It protects you through proxy servers. Keeps you anonymous.
接下來我來演示如何進入
Then I'll show you how to get to
論壇和即時聊天
the posting boards and the IRCs.
但我要提醒你  不要隨便亂點
But I gotta warn you: Be careful what you click.
這上面有些很瘋狂的東西
Some crazy shit there, man.
長久以來
For too long, uh, we've, uh,
我們對網路戰一事小心翼翼
danced on egg shells regarding the issue of cyber warfare.
杜蘭特國務卿
Now, Secretary Durant
是按照我的指令行事
acted on instructions that came directly from me.
如果中國沒有誠意
Now, if the Chinese are not willing to
進行一場有意義的對話
engage in a meaningful dialogue
探討美國公司的智慧財產權
about intellectual property of American corporations
以及對我政府網路設施的
as well as this deliberate targeting
蓄意攻擊
of our government's online infrastructure,
那就證明他們抱有一種雙重標準的心態
well then that is proof of a double-standard mentality
而我們將不再容忍這種心態
that we shall no longer tolerate.
我們派往商貿聯合委員會的代表
Our delegation to the Joint Commission on Commerce and Trade
遭到了美國政府代表的
was unfairly accused and defamed
不公平指控與汙衊
by representatives of the United States government.
中華人民共和國
The People's Republic of China
不會受
will not be threatened
荒謬而未經證實的指控所脅迫
by derisive and unsubstantiated claims.
如果白宮還要繼續如此行事
As long as the White House continues to behave this way,
那麼將來任何的雙邊對話都是不可能的
any future bilateral trade talks will be impossible.
我也覺得大吃一驚
It caught me by surprise, too.
昨天我掛電話之後  你又對他說什麼了嗎
Did you say anything to him after I hung up yesterday?
沒有  你跟他談過了嗎
No. Have you spoken to him?
是的  幾分鐘前
Yeah, a few minutes ago.
他說他做了他認為該做的事
He said he did what he thought was right.
這我們沒法反駁
Well, there's nothing we can do to combat that.
他一般不會招呼都不打
He doesn't usually go against my advice
就違揹我的建議
without giving me fair warning.
你什麼意思  雷蒙德
What are you suggesting, Raymond?
他容易受人操縱
He's easily manipulated.
這次不是
Clearly not in this case.
這問題必須解決  就指望你了  弗蘭克
We need to fix this. And I'm counting on you for that, Frank.
我再說一遍  我不欠你什麼
Let me freshen your memory. I don't owe you any favors.
我答應跟你合作  不是給你賣力
I promised to work with you, not for you.
對於中國的問題  我們的目標一樣
And when it comes to China, we both want the same thing.
所以得合作
So we need to work together.
說服加勒特撤回言論
To convince Garrett he should retract.
是支援總統的選擇
To support the president in the path that he's chosen.
他可是在公然挑釁
While he continues to antagonize them publicly.
他這是持續贏得民眾認可
While he continues to benefit from a bump in approval ratings.
對中的強硬政策很吃香的
A tough stance on China is popular.
這點可以加以利用
And we can use that to our advantage.
耐心點
Let's just be patient
我儘量暗中調解一下
and see if we can smooth things over from back channels.
我的耐心是有限的  儘快讓我看到成果
If I don't see any results, you won't have my patience for long.
我知道了
That's understood.
杜蘭特的話記得告訴我
Let me know what Durant has to say.
當然
Absolutely.
謝謝你  副總統先生
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
我以為他不會願意接受我的恩惠呢
I thought he might balk at taking a handout from me.
這可不是小恩小惠
I'd call it more than a handout.
他向來不難收買
Well, he's always been the sort of man
只是代價一直很大
who could be bought, but never cheaply.
贏得他的不是主席位子  泰德
It's not the chairmanship that bought him, Ted.
什麼意思
What do you mean?
我現在告訴你
I'm telling you this
是給你時間跟你妻子談
so that you have time to call your wife
並且準備發言稿
and prepare your statement.
我怎麼脫身  他要幹什麼
What's my out? What does he want from me?
脫不了  他就想傷你
There is no out. He wants it to hurt.
你跟他說的
You told him.
我只是說可以辦到
I just promised him that I could make it happen.
你不能這麼做  傑姬
You can't do this, Jackie.
明天報導就見報
The story's breaking tomorrow.
哪部分
What part of it?
不提名字  只說你有私生女
No names. Just that you have a daughter.
你想沒想過對戴安的影響  對我們的兒子
Have you thought about what this will do to Diane? To our sons?
我並不覺得光彩
I hate myself for it.
可是我能撐過去
But I'll get over that.
那她呢
What about her?
艾米莉  你連名字都不敢說嗎
Emily. You can't even say her name, can you?
少教育我
Don't lecture me.
你都沒跟她共處過
You've never been in the same room with her.
我給她提供了最好的醫療條件
She's had the best treatment available.
一個人  滿身的儀器連線
Alone. Hooked up to machines.
晚飯之後就沒有護士了
Surrounded by nurses who punch out at dinnertime.
你不知道我有多難過
You don't know what I've been through.
你  那她呢
You? What about her?
我已經盡力了
I can't do more than I've done.
胡說  泰德  你有辦法的
That's bullshit, Ted. You could've found a way.
我不會向你為自己辯護
I won't defend myself to you.
不用  跟你老婆說吧
Don't. Save that for your wife.
我不是要懲罰你  泰德
This isn't to punish you, Ted.
比那簡單
It's -- it's simpler than that.
當初我鼓勵你參選
When I first encouraged you to run for office,
是覺得你不達目的不罷休
it's because I sensed how unstoppable you were.
可沒想到連我你都可以犧牲
But I never thought I'd have to lie down on the tracks myself.
你要是想弄死我
If you're going to put my neck in the noose,
動手時要看著我的眼睛
look me in the eye while you do it.
你對我的付出我很感激
I'm very grateful for all that you've done for me.
你能做個好黨鞭  傑奎琳
You'll make an excellent whip, Jacqueline.
滾出我的辦公室吧
Now please get out of my office.
你幹什麼呢
What are you doing?
終於清靜了
It's finally quiet.
可不是嗎
It is, isn't it?
這是咱倆的堡壘了
We have our fortress now.
你去哪了
Where are you coming from?
新辦公室  今天剛裝修完
My new office. They just finished setting it up today.
喜歡嗎
Do you like it?
就是間辦公室  湊合吧
It's an office. It's fine.
昵稱  Data_Crusader  主題  需要獲取通話記錄
昵稱  Data_Crusader  主題  需要獲取通話記錄  內容  美國副總統
■
2013年6月7至8日  中美兩國元首在加州進行了舉世矚目的"莊園峰會"
峰會舉行前  美國媒體普遍認為網路安全將成會晤焦點問題
從2013年初  美國政府和國會中的外交界鷹派便一直要求白宮
在網路安全上向中國施壓  採取強硬立場
可就在"莊園峰會"舉行前一天  英國《衛報》首次向外界披露了
美國國家安全局大規模蒐集民眾通訊記錄的"稜鏡計劃"
從那時起到現在的九個多月內
美國情報機構的祕密檔案仍在源源不斷地被媒體披露出來
美國政府也一直忙於向世界其它國家解釋自己的監聽計劃
再也顧不上就網路安全問題上對中國指手畫腳
■
國會有影響力的議員職務變動後  填補空缺時往往會如劇中演繹的那樣
帶來一系列的連鎖反應  甚至引發大的政治醜聞
2008年總統選舉後  伊利諾伊州參議員歐巴馬當選總統
負責指派接替歐巴馬參議員職務的伊利諾依伊州長
試圖私下叫賣這個肥缺  結果事情敗露  最後鋃鐺入獄
比較近的一個例子是  駐華大使駱家輝辭職後
歐巴馬欽點蒙大拿州參議員鮑卡斯接替駱家輝的大使職務
而鮑卡斯赴任北京後留下的參議院財政委員會主席的位置由誰來接任
將很大程度上影響民主黨在參議院的權力佈局和年底中期選舉的結果
據美國媒體報道  幫助鮑卡斯獲得駐華大使空缺的正是他的老朋友副總統拜登